[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "(a:number, b: number): _____? => a < b",
    "options": ["string", "number", "boolean"],
    "answer": "boolean"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "let name: _____? = \"Mike\"",
    "options": ["number", "boolean", "string"],
    "answer": "string"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "const namesArr: _____? = [\"JavaScript\",\"C#\",\"Python\"]",
    "options": ["string[]", "string", "boolean[]"],
    "answer": "string[]"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "let myVar: unknown = \"Hello world!\";\nconsole.log(_____?.length)",
    "options": ["string", "<boolean>myVar", "<string>myVar"],
    "answer": "<string>myVar"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "{myVar = 5}:{myVar: _____?}",
    "options": ["string[]", "boolean", "number"],
    "answer": "number"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "(a: _____?,b: string) => a + b",
    "options": ["string[]", "boolean", "number"],
    "answer": "string"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "(a: _____?,b: number) => a + b",
    "options": ["string[]", "boolean", "number"],
    "answer": "number"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "const namesArr: _____? = ['1','2','3','4','5','6']",
    "options": ["string[]", "string", "boolean[]"],
    "answer": "string[]"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "const namesArr: _____? = [1,2,3,4,5]",
    "options": ["string[]", "number[]", "number"],
    "answer": "number[]"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "(a:number, b: number): _____? => a === b",
    "options": ["string", "number", "boolean"],
    "answer": "boolean"
  }
]
